<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Case Studies on Green Zero Development</title>
    <link>https://greenzero-2019.netlify.com/case-study/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Case Studies on Green Zero Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://greenzero-2019.netlify.com/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FEMAC</title>
      <link>https://greenzero-2019.netlify.com/case-study/femac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greenzero-2019.netlify.com/case-study/femac/</guid>
      <description>Discovery How can we improve FEMAC&#39;s web experience?  FEMAC Security Solutions was one of greenZero&#39;s first clients and a bit of a different case from what was to come in the following years. FEMAC has never requested editing access and prefers to lean on greenZero&#39;s expertise for updating their website&#39;s content. We decided to use this unique arrangement to maximize hosting savings and streamline the developer experience on FEMAC&#39;s website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnPoint Custom Homes</title>
      <link>https://greenzero-2019.netlify.com/case-study/onpoint-custom-homes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greenzero-2019.netlify.com/case-study/onpoint-custom-homes/</guid>
      <description>Discovery What did the client need help with?  OnPoint Custom Homes was suffering from long load times that annoyed and drove away customers who were landing on their site via the company&#39;s marketing efforts. They needed a fix and they needed it fast. greenZero was brought on to figure out how to speed up the site while keeping all of the important editing power OPCH had with their existing backend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remediant</title>
      <link>https://greenzero-2019.netlify.com/case-study/remediant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greenzero-2019.netlify.com/case-study/remediant/</guid>
      <description>Discovery What was causing trouble?  When greenZero was brought on to help the project, Remediant was wrestling with their previous content management system. Their CMS solution wasn&#39;t particularly bad (it had all of the tools you&#39;d expect from a CMS), but it forced Remediant to adhere to design and development standards the company wasn&#39;t comfortable with.
The endgame was definitely to transition off of Remediant&#39;s constricting CMS solution, but before any work could be done we had to agree on three important things.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>